# Carmen Ng

#### Web Developer

An adaptable and motivated individual with a strong understanding of visual communications currently working as a Solutions Developer. Over 3 years of web development experience has allowed me to develop strong analytical and problem solving skills. I am eager to continue learning new skills and gain more experience in various areas and languages as I am always striving for self improvement, both professionally and personally.

carmenng.media@gmail.com

Hong Kong

in linkedin.com/in/carng

Available via Email

nightlightvisuals.com

github.com/CarNg

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Senior Software Engineer**

OpenRice 🗷

09/2019 - Present Hong Kong

 Working as part of the Web Team developing company websites such as OpenRice.com and Biz.OpenRice.com

## **Solutions Developer**

PCCW Solutions

04/2017 - 09/2019

Hong Kong

Hong Kong

- Redesign and develop frontend (JSP, JavaScript, jQuery and CSS) for clients' exisiting ERP systems.
- Work directly with BAs to design and develop more user friendly flows and enhancements.
- API connection to existing Oracle E-Business ERP (Java).

#### Full Stack Developer

Tree in total gy radas riotaling Eta.

RT-Technology is behind BabyPOS POS system. In addition to POS products, they also provide services in web design & development and SEO optimisation.

- Develop and manage the POS system's responsive web platform.
- Connect the POS system's API to clients' online shops' API allowing live updates between the two.
- Design and develop clients' websites and online shops.
- Design and develop internal sites that were used by sales team and for marketing purposes.

Contact: Raymond Tse - raymond@babypos.hk

## **SKILLS**

Vue.js Less

Node.js Bootstrap

.NET jQuery

React PhotoShop

## **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

Night Light Visuals (2015 - Present)

 Night Light Visuals is my personal branding and portfolio site for my previous and current projects. The website is built using React.js

#### This Time Around (02/2014 - 02/2015)

 'This Time Around' is an interactive fiction/exploration game developed as a MSc final project. My responsibilities included game design (mechanics & aesthetics), narrative creation, programming using C# in Unity3D, sound design, QA, testing with users and analysing results, marketing the game, write a full report detailing the process of game development from research to final product.

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Best Game Script Nominee (06/2018)

Nominated for a Writers' Guild of Ireland ZeBBie Award in Best Game Script as a co-writer of Simteractive's Eden Isle: Resort Paradise

## LANGUAGES

English Cantonese

Native or Bilingual Proficiency Professional Working Proficiency

## **EDUCATION**

## **MSc in Creative Digital Media**

Dublin Institute of Technology

09/2013 - 02/2015

First Class Honours

## BA (Hons) Journalism and Visual Media

Griffith College Dublin 🕝

09/2009 - 07/2012 First Class Honours

## INTERESTS

Bouldering | Boxing

Videography

Gaming

Music

Travelling